Naruemol Detprasert

12/48 Metroluxe Phaholyothin Condo, Soi Inthamara 14 Alley, Sutthisan Winitchai Rd, Samsennai, Phayathai, Bangkok 10400

Mobile: +66 98 5624251

Email: naruemol_det@hotmail.com



OBJECTIVE

To have the opportunity to contribute and utilize my extensive knowledge and experiences to organizational effectiveness, and also to have the opportunity for career advancement and challenge.

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

10+ years experience in data analysis in the areas of membership management, campaign marketing, and health risk behavior in the healthcare business A project manager to manage projects on time and on budget. Manage risk and issues, including preparing management status reports.

A manager with the ability to manage office functions and direct administrative personnel to meet the needs of executives Performance-oriented and driven with an in-depth understanding of budgets, payroll, and office organization needs. Skillfully coordinate resources and administrative support to keep operations smooth and boost team productivity.

SKILLS

Project Management & Self-motivation Business Analysis Analytical Thinking Research Project Support Multitasking / Problem-solving Interpersonal skills Team leadership Organizational skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PRASIT PATANA PUBLIC COMPANY LIMITED
Health Information Management Manager,
Human Resources - The Phyathai-Paolo Hospital Group
Aug 2020 - Present

- Analyze and present guidelines to prepare strategic plans and operational plans that are consistent with the goals, vision, and mission of the company.
- Manage innovation development projects for the Health Intervention team from activation to first shipment.
- Conversion of Opportunity Advantages to a New or Strengthened Product.
- Forecast and manage a budget, plan year, and performance.
- Create a project work plan and maintain a detailed project plan, including project changes.
- Manage workforce.
- Collaborate with the project team members, stakeholders, and champions to identify business requirements and develop projects.

- Research and transform information from raw data into an easily understood analysis that identifies trends and insights for the organization.
- Discover industry trends based on data collection methods and analysis strategies, and use the information to help the company make production and product adjustments to increase efficiency by 5 percent.
- Pinpoint a set of variables to evaluate and work with when deciding on the range of analysis and scope of information sought.
- Use a variety of sources inside and outside of the company to collect, aggregate, and analyze data
- Work with the Let's Get Healthy! (LGH) steering committee and LGH core team to drive innovation and technology in the BDMS Group.
- Coordinate with external vendors and startup teams for new solutions and innovation in health intervention.
- Prepare weekly status reports for all stakeholders.
- Prepare change requests for projects out of scope.
- Monitor the progress of the project and make adjustments as necessary.
- Communicate and coordinate with vendors to support and work alignment with the project plan.

GET Health Mobile Application

Working as a project manager for a mobile application used by the Phyathai-Paolo Hospital group. Develop a project plan and activities. Review the project status report, including risks and issues. Monitor the progress of the project and make adjustments as necessary. Manage vendors, including the internal IT team, to ensure all the tasks are delivered on time and on schedule with quality.

Let's Get Healthy! Application

Working as a project manager for an LGH mobile application used by the BDMS Team. Testing systems and issue resolution ensured the deliverables were on time and of high quality. Review project status reports, including risks and issues. Monitor the progress of the project and make adjustments as necessary. Manage vendors, including the internal IT team, to ensure all the tasks are delivered on time and on schedule with quality.

PHYATHAI 2 HOSPITAL Health Management Database and Database Marketing Manager, Corporate Sales. Jan 2010 - July 2020

- Oversaw and managed all operational, administrative, and functional matters of the department.
- Ensured operations were managed successfully, ensuring maximum corporate client and customer satisfaction consistent with the mission through planning, organizing, directing, and controlling all department operations.
- Managed and controlled budget under responsibility within the plan and generated total cost savings in responsible areas.
- Achieved optimum operating results, constantly endeavoring to improve the standards of the department.
- Developed well-trained staff with high morale and loyalty.
- Handled customer complaints, special requests, and inquiries efficiently and professionally.
- Developed and implemented lean process concepts that reduced material waste by 10-15%.
- Supervised and coached subordinates on tasks, and shared and advised on problem-solving solutions to ensure job completeness and smooth implementation.
- Managed Workforce

Phyathai Intouch Mobile Application

Worked with team leads on a mobile application used for the Phyathai 2 Hospital. Developed a project plan and activities. Reviewed the project status report, including risks and issues. Monitor the progress of the project and make adjustments as necessary. Managed vendors, including the internal IT team, to ensure all the tasks were delivered on time and on schedule with quality.

Health Check Doctors in Web-Base Application

Worked with physicians and the Occupational Health team on a web-based application that was used for the Phyathai 2 Hospital. Developed a project plan and activities. Reviewed the project status report, including risks and issues. Monitored the progress of the project and made adjustments as necessary. Managed vendors, including the internal IT team, to ensure all the tasks were delivered on time and on schedule with quality.

PRASIT PATANA PUBLIC COMPANY LIMITED Aug 2007 - Dec 2009

Database Marketing, Marketing - The Phyathai Hospital Group

- Analyzed current and past patient data to come up with effective CRM campaigns and mechanics for each customer's life cycle.
- Interpreted information from a series of database investigations to make predictions and recommendations for a company's scope of work.
- Discussed results of database analysis with various members of management in an organization and led staff members to realize the significance of the data.
- Managed the client database, ensuring data accuracy, cleanliness, and compliance with data protection regulations.
- Segment the customer database to identify target audiences for marketing campaigns and personalized communication.
- Analyzed and mapped customer journeys to understand touchpoints and conversion opportunities.
- Tracked campaign performance, and customer behavior, and analyzed CRM data. To optimize strategies, generate reports, and offer insights.

PRASIT PATANA PUBLIC COMPANY LIMITED Junior Customer Relationship Management (CRM), Business Development - The Phyathai Hospital Group Dec 2004 - July 2007

- Planned, executed, and monitored CRM campaigns, including email marketing, direct mail marketing, and other channels of communication.
- Collected and analyzed customer feedback and surveys to identify areas for improvement and gain insights for enhancing the customer experience.
- Managed the client database, ensuring data accuracy, cleanliness, and compliance with data protection regulations.
- Worked closely with cross-functional teams, including marketing, sales, and IT, to align CRM initiatives with enterprise-wide objectives.

Membership Management in Web-Base Application

Worked as a K@pook! vendor and development IT team for a web-based application that was used for the Phyathai Hospital Group. Offered marketing teams training and support on CRM tools and service providers, if necessary.

EDUCATION

Master of Health Business Management (HBM), College of Management Mahidol University, 2023 Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A), Advertising and Public Relations Major. Ramkhamhaeng University, 2000

TRAINING / CERTIFICATE

- Certificate of Data Science Pathway
- Certificate of Human Research Participated Protection Course
- People Management Skills for the Leader
- Tableau Desktop Fundamental & Advance Software
- The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People
- FTE Workforce Management
- Feasibility & Investment Proposal